<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018 FiatAcompli -->
<xsl:stylesheet version="1.0" xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">
  <xsl:output method="xml" encoding="utf-8" indent="yes"/>
  <xsl:strip-space elements="*"/>

  <xsl:include href="../modinfo_fixer_base.xml"/>

  <xsl:template match="/Mod/Properties">
    <xsl:copy>
      <xsl:apply-templates select="@*|node()"/>
    </xsl:copy>
    <LocalizedText>
      <xsl:call-template name="GenerateText">
        <xsl:with-param name="identifier">LOC_DISTRICT_COST_REWORK_MOD_NAME</xsl:with-param>
        <xsl:with-param name="is_mod_name" select="true()"/>
        <xsl:with-param name="base">Distict Cost Rework</xsl:with-param>
      </xsl:call-template>
      <xsl:call-template name="GenerateText">
        <xsl:with-param name="identifier">LOC_DISTRICT_COST_REWORK_TEASER</xsl:with-param>
        <xsl:with-param name="base">Reworks district cost to be based on number of districts already built and city size rather than game (tech/civic) progression.</xsl:with-param>
      </xsl:call-template>
      <xsl:call-template name="GenerateText">
        <xsl:with-param name="identifier">LOC_DISTRICT_COST_REWORK_DESCRIPTION</xsl:with-param>
        <xsl:with-param name="base">District cost is now based on the number of districts of that type previously built by a civilization as well as the number of specialty districts (of any type) already present in the city.  The intent is that it should still be possible in the late game to found a new city and get districts up and running fairly quickly (particularly if your empire is small).

Changes:
* District cost no longer scales with game time or has catchup mechanisms relative to other civs.
* District cost scales based on the number of previous districts of that type constructed by the civilization. Each district constructed adds 40% of the base cost of a district to future constructions of that district. (Neighborhoods, spaceports, etc are still fixed cost.)
* Building a district in a city with 1/2/3/.../10 specialty districts already built increases district cost by 10/25/45/70/100/140/180/220/260/300%.
* Removes Reyna's Contractor promotion for buying districts with gold since the production scaling described above does not affect the converted gold cost, so districts would be unreasonably cheap to purchase. (And, honestly, because I simply don't like the district purchase mechanic.)
* New promotion for Reyna - Free Trader:
  * Adds +2 gold to outgoing international trade routes.
  * Adds +2 gold for both parties to incoming international trade routes.</xsl:with-param>
      </xsl:call-template>
    </LocalizedText>
  </xsl:template>
  
</xsl:stylesheet>